

Contacts

Telephone

+39 340 860 164 6

Email

giovanni-sorrentino@hotmail.it

Address

PAVULLO NEL FRIGNANO (MODENA) ITALY

Linkedin

Giovanni Sorentino Linkedin

Github

Giovanni Sorrentino Github

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- SAAS
- BOTSTRAP
- JAVASCRIPT
- VITE
- VUE.JS
- PHP
- MySQL
- LARAVEL

Languages

Italian(Mother Tongue)

English (B1)

Spanish (B1)

Giovanni Sorrentino

JR FULL-Stack web Developer

While I was in school, I got introduced to the programming of CNC machines. After several years of practice in the field, I realized that I really enjoyed the programming itself. To improve myself, I wanted to use more innovative and versatile tools. Therefore I started a six-month course at the Boolean institute. Here I was able to accomplish my aspirations and improve and broaden my programming skills.

Experience

O 24/01/2024 - 17/07/2024

BOOLEAN

(Training for) Jr Full-Stack Web Developer

- I created a Portfolio application in which I included all my projects.
 The storage was managed by **GitHub** on the backend. Visitors were able to view the finished work from my training with Boolean.
- Further, I created an app similar to Airbnb with a team, Using PHP,
 MySQL and Laravel. It allowed registered users to add apartments.
 For the frontend, Vue.js and JavaScript was used. Unregistered users were able to view the apartments and contact the owners for information.
- 0 11/01/2021 15/12/2023

P.M.P s.r.l

Operator and Programmer

- CNC machine programmer and personal work organization
- Direct Communication with Department Managers
- Time Management and making sure to meet the deadlines

25/08/2019 - 25/02/2020

BOSCH REXOROT

Quality Control Inspector

- Reporting issues found on products from production
- Problem-solving in collaboration with managers and engineers
- Knowledge of measurement and inspection tools related to products

EDUCATION

BOOLEAN

24/01/2024 - 17/07/2024

• Six-month intensive program where I gained skills in key frontend and backend languages / 700-hour accelerated course that includes theoretical lessons in the morning and practical activities in the afternoon.

IIS GUGLIELMO MARCONI PAVULLO

15/09/2014 - 12/07/2019

• Five-year educational high school program where I obtained a diploma as a Maintenance Technician and Technical Assistant.